export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Who is considered to be the father of modern economics?",
    options: [
      "Adam Smith",
      "Karl Marx",
      "John Maynard Keynes",
      "David Ricardo",
    ],
    answer: "Adam Smith",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "Which economic school of thought is associated with the idea of laissez-faire?",
    options: [
      "Keynesian economics",
      "Monetarism",
      "Classical economics",
      "Austrian economics",
    ],
    answer: "Austrian economics",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a factor of production?",
    options: ["Land", "Labor", "Money", "Capital"],
    answer: "Money",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question:
      "What is the term used to describe the total value of all goods and services produced in a country in a given period of time?",
    options: [
      "Gross Domestic Product (GDP)",
      "Net Domestic Product (NDP)",
      "Gross National Income (GNI)",
      "Gross National Product (GNP)",
    ],
    answer: "Gross Domestic Product (GDP)",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of market structure?",
    options: ["Monopoly", "Oligopoly", "Monopsony", "Plutocracy"],
    answer: "Plutocracy",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of unemployment?",
    options: [
      "Frictional unemployment",
      "Structural unemployment",
      "Cyclical unemployment",
      "Inflationary unemployment",
    ],
    answer: "Inflationary unemployment",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of inflation?",
    options: [
      "Demand-pull inflation",
      "Cost-push inflation",
      "Hyperinflation",
      "Paradoxical inflation",
    ],
    answer: "Paradoxical inflation",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of fiscal policy?",
    options: [
      "Expansionary fiscal policy",
      "Contractionary fiscal policy",
      "Monetary fiscal policy",
      "Automatic stabilizers",
    ],
    answer: "Monetary fiscal policy",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of monetary policy?",
    options: [
      "Expansionary monetary policy",
      "Contractionary monetary policy",
      "Quantitative easing",
      "Fiscal policy",
    ],
    answer: "Fiscal policy",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of trade barrier?",
    options: ["Tariff", "Quota", "Subsidy", "Free trade"],
    answer: "Free trade",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which economist created and described surplus value?",
    options: [
      "David Ricardo",
      "Karl Marx",
      "John Maynard Keynes",
      "Adam Smith",
    ],
    answer: "Karl Marx",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "What describes the Kuznets curve?",
    options: [
      "The relationship between income inequality and economic growth",
      "The relationship between inflation and unemployment",
      "The relationship between interest rates and investment",
      "The relationship between government spending and economic growth",
    ],
    answer: "The relationship between income inequality and economic growth",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of economic system?",
    options: ["Capitalism", "Socialism", "Fascism", "Communism"],
    answer: "Fascism",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of market failure?",
    options: ["Perfect competition", "Monopoly", "Oligopoly", "Monopsony"],
    answer: "Perfect competition",
  },
];

export const currencyQuizQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "What currency is in the picture?",
    image: "",
    options: ["USD", "EUR", "GBP", "JPY"],
    answer: "USD",
  },
];
